https://www.usicerinks.org/privacy-policy

HomeJoin Today!MembersIndividual Member ProfileFacility Member ProfileVendor Member ProfileDues, Invoices & ReceiptsEducationCoursesLocations / RegistrationCertificationsCurrent Certified ProfessionalsConferenceEvent ScheduleEducationTradeshowHost HotelSponsorsResourcesRink MagazineIssue ArchiveAdvertiseVendor Member DirectoryClassifiedsCOVID-19Indoor Air QualityR-22 Phase OutRulebooks & DiagramsAbout UsLeadershipStaffPartnersAllied Members
Member Login
719.538.1149
TestimonialsContact Us
HomeJoin Today!MembersIndividual Member ProfileFacility Member ProfileVendor Member ProfileDues, Invoices & ReceiptsEducationCoursesLocations / RegistrationCertificationsCurrent Certified ProfessionalsConferenceEvent ScheduleEducationTradeshowHost HotelSponsorsResourcesRink MagazineIssue ArchiveAdvertiseVendor Member DirectoryClassifiedsCOVID-19Indoor Air QualityR-22 Phase OutRulebooks & DiagramsAbout UsLeadershipStaffPartnersAllied Members
Privacy Policy
HomePrivacy Policy
This Privacy Statement governs your use of starrinks.com and usicerinks.com.
These Web sites (these “Sites”) are owned and operated by Serving The American Rinks dba Unites States Ice Rink Association (“STAR,” “we” or “us”). STAR is a membership organization for individuals, facilities and vendors in the American ice rink industry.
This Online Privacy Statement.
We are committed to respecting the personal privacy of the individuals who use our Sites.
This online Privacy Statement (this “Privacy Statement”) describes our current policies and practices with regard to the personal information we collect through our Sites.
The term “personal information” means individually identifiable information about an individual collected through our Sites, including without limitation, the name, age, telephone number, e-mail address, mailing address, or other information of that individual provided through any of our Sites.
Children Under 13.
We recognize the need to provide additional privacy protections for children who visit our Sites. To read about our privacy statement regarding protections for children who are under 13, click here. We do not permit individuals under the age of 13 to place orders on our Sites or to engage in certain activities on our Sites without the permission of a parent or guardian.
Terms of Use
This Privacy Statement is part of the Terms of Use for our Sites.
Please be sure to read the Terms of Use.
By using our Sites, you agree to be bound by the Terms of Use.
If you do not agree to the Terms of Use, you must not use our Sites.
Your Consent.
By using any of our Sites, you consent to the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Statement.
If you do not consent to the terms of this Privacy Statement, you must not use our Sites.
Changes to this Privacy Statement.
This Privacy Statement describes our current policies and practices regarding personal information collected through our Sites.
We reserve the right to update or modify this Privacy Statement at any time without prior notice.
We will do so by posting an updated or modified version of this Privacy Statement on our Sites.
Your use of any of our Sites following any such change constitutes your agreement that personal information collected from or about you through our Sites after the revised Privacy Statement is posted will be subject to the terms of the revised Privacy Statement.
For this reason, we encourage you to review this Privacy Statement regularly.
You may access the current version of this Privacy Statement by clicking on the button marked “Privacy Statement.”
This Privacy Statement was last revised on March 23, 2017.
What Personal Information Is Collected Through Our Sites. We collect the personal information you supply when you use our Sites, for example, the information you provide when you register for membership in STAR or register for an event on any of our Sites, request an e-mail newsletter, ask a question, enter a contest or sweepstakes or complete a survey.
This information may include your name, your address, your e-mail address and any other personal or preference information you share with us.
How We Use Personal Information.
We use your personal information to provide the information, offerings and services you request, confirm your membership to STAR or your registration to an event.
For example, we use your e-mail address to respond to your comments and questions or to send e-mail newsletters.
We may use your personal information to personalize our Sites to meet your specific needs.
We also use personal information collected through our Sites to improve the content and functionality of our Sites, to better understand our visitors and members, to improve our offerings and services, and to market our events, offerings and services to our visitors and members.
In addition, we use personal information to contact you with offers and information about events, offerings and services from other organizations that we believe will be of interest to you.
If you would prefer that we not contact you for such purposes, you may indicate this preference by sending an email to info@usicerinks.com or by writing us at:
Serving The American Rinks dba United States Ice Rink Association
1775 Bob Johnson Drive Colorado Springs, CO 80906 Attn.: Member Services.
We will use reasonable efforts to honor such requests.
You must understand, however, that even if you “opt-out,” you may still receive communications from us, for example, if we receive your contact information from another source or if we initiated the communication before we received your “opt-out” request.
Disclosure of Personal Information.
We share personal information collected through our Sites with our affiliated organizations (such as USA Hockey and U.S. Figure Skating).
If you would prefer that we not share your personal information with our affiliated organizations, you may indicate this preference by sending an email to info@starrinks.com or by writing us at:
Serving The American Rinks dba United States Ice Rink Association
1775 Bob Johnson Drive Colorado Springs, CO 80906 Attn.: Member Services.
We will use reasonable efforts to honor such requests.
You must understand, however, that even if you “opt-out,” you may still receive communications from our affiliated organizations or business partners, for example, if they received your contact information from another source or if they initiated the communication before we received your “opt-out” request.
We share personal information collected through our Sites with third party vendors who act for us or on our behalf, for example, to help us process or fill your orders, run promotions or provide other support services.
Our affiliates and our business partners may also share personal information with vendors who provide support services to them.
These vendors need information about you in order to perform their functions.
These vendors are not authorized to use the information we share with them (or that our affiliates and business partners share with them) for any purpose other than to provide services to us, our affiliates or our business partners.
STAR has engaged certain third party service providers to perform services on behalf of STAR in connection with the management and operation of certain features of our Sites (including without limitation operation of our Sites’ registration functionality).
In addition, there may be some other, limited circumstances in which we may share or transfer personal information in our databases to a third party, for example, to comply with a legal requirement, for the administration of justice, to protect the security of our systems or service, or in the event of a merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar event.
Other Information Collected Through Our Sites. We use technology that tells us how visitors use our Sites, for example, which pages they view, which links they use and which search terms they input.
This information is called “click-stream data.”
Click-stream data helps us determine what is important to you and what is not.
It helps us decide what content and features to add and what to discard.
It also helps us determine whether our Site is easy to use or whether we need to redesign certain pages and links.
Click-stream data does not identify you personally.
We also use technology to collect the following information and other information of a similar nature:
the name of your Internet service provider; your IP address; your operating system (Windows, Macintosh, Unix, and so on); and your browser type (Netscape, Internet Explorer, and so on).
We use this information to compile statistics about the technology used by our visitors.
These statistics help us improve our Site and make it more compatible with the technology used by our visitors.
Cookies. Our Sites uses certain software technology known as “cookies.”
Cookies are small text files that a web site places on a visitor’s computer browser to store certain information about the visitor, such as a visitor’s preferences.
Some web browsers provide you with the ability to turn off or refuse cookies.
However, if you turn off cookies or refuse cookies, some of the features of our Sites may not function properly.
Links to Other Web Sites.
This privacy policy applies only to our Sites. These Sites contain links to other web sites, including those of advertisers, sponsors and vendor members.
These other web sites have their own policies regarding privacy. We urge you to review the privacy policy posted on any site you visit before using the site or providing any personal information about yourself.
In addition, you may have linked to one of our Sites through another site. For example, in certain cases you may have linked to one of our Sites through banner advertising on another site.
In such cases, the site you linked from may collect information from people who click on the banner or link. You may want to refer to the privacy policies on those sites to see how they collect and use this information.
Security To protect your credit card number and other personal information when you register for membership or an event we use Authorize.net encryption technology. Your credit card number is digitally scrambled to ensure that is not read by unauthorized third parties. If you're still concerned about internet security, please contact our customer service department to submit your order by telephone or fax. Although we will use all reasonable efforts to safeguard the confidentiality of any visitor information collected on our Sites, STAR and its vendors will have no liability for disclosure of any visitor information obtained due to errors in transmission or the unauthorized acts of third parties.
Transfer of Data Abroad. If you are visiting our Sites from a country other than the countries in which our servers are located (currently the United States), the placing of an order in our Store, or other various communications may necessarily result in the transfer of information across international boundaries. By visiting our Sites and communicating electronically with us, you consent to the processing and transfer of your data as set out in this Privacy Policy.
Accessing and Updating Your Information. You always have the opportunity to review and change the information you provide to us by logging into our Sites and entering in the new information yourself. You can edit your name, contact information and preferences by logging into the applicable account management section of starrinks.com or usicerinks.com.
You may ask to have your account information removed from our active databases; however, because we keep track of past purchases, we cannot delete information associated with past purchases. Also, as a security measure we "back up" the data stored on our systems, and such prior information cannot be completely removed from our databases. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your personal information will be completely removed from our databases in response to your requests.
Questions About This Privacy Statement.
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement or concerns about the way we process your personal information, please contact us at:
Serving The American Rinks dba United States Ice Rink Association
1775 Bob Johnson Drive, Colorado Springs, CO 80906 | Attn: Member Services.
or (719) 538-1149
or fax at (719) 538-7838
or info@usicerinks.com
THE PREMIER ANNUAL EVENT FOR THE ICE RINK INDUSTRY
Our 18th annual educational conference and trade show will take place May 18-21, 2021 in Buffalo, NY. NARCE gives you the unique opportunity to expand your knowledge and network with professionals from around North America. Registration starts January 1, 2021
Learn More
Upcoming Events
Check our Calendar for Events
and Courses Nearby
See Calender
Stay Connected
Keep Up-to-date with our
recent Social Media feeds
Get Social:
